[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before playing Arthur Leigh Allen (Zodiac) in the film Zodiac, actor John Carroll Lynch starred in what TV show?", "correct_answer": "The Drew Carey Show", "incorrect_answers": ["Frasier", "Seinfeld", "Mad About You"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In olden days urine was recycled.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played bank robber Smiler Grogan in Its a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World?", "correct_answer": "Jimmy Durante", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Knotts", "Buster Keaton", "Jack Benny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Spinach is extremely rich in antioxidants.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before raw, unprocessed chocolate becomes suitable for eating, It has to be stirred and kneaded using equipment with rollers, in a process called what?", "correct_answer": "Conching", "incorrect_answers": ["Molding", "Mashing", "Sparging"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the horrible creature, whose name literally translates as goat-sucker from Spanish?", "correct_answer": "Chupacabra", "incorrect_answers": ["Chimera", "Kitsune", "Cthulhu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the division of Korea into two parts?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Korea was divided at the 38th parallel.", "North Korea was to be administered by the Soviet union.", "It followed the end of World War II."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these airplane disasters is considered the deadliest in history?", "correct_answer": "The destruction of the World Trade Center", "incorrect_answers": ["The Charkhi Dadri mid-air collision", "The Tenerife disaster", "The Hawaiian disaster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the senses of zebras is generally underdeveloped and the animal cannot rely very much on it?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Smell", "Hearing", "Eyesight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Hunt for Red October, Jack Ryan is asked to give a briefing at the White House. What is the name of the National Security Advisor who is leading the meeting?", "correct_answer": "Jeffrey Pelt", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard Jordan", "Donald Richardson", "Oliver Holmes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During this year, the USA had three different Presidents.", "correct_answer": "1841", "incorrect_answers": ["1864", "1844", "1973"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the Ghostbusters movies was released in 1989?", "correct_answer": "Ghostbusters II", "incorrect_answers": ["Ghostbusters III", "None of these", "Ghostbusters"]}]